
/****************************************************************************
The classicly (bad) "Lost in Space" is being rebooted by Netflix this weekend
Let's create an object that holds the question and answers
*****************************************************************************/
var lostInSpaceArray = [
    {
       Question : "What is the destination of the Jupiter 2 and the Robinson Family?" ,
       Answer : "Alpha Centauri"
    },
    {
        Question : "Who Composed the theme Song?" ,
        Answer : "John Williams"
     },
     {
        Question : "Guy Williams was also famous for what role?" ,
        Answer : "Zorro"
     },
     {
         Question:"Name the first actress to recieve NASA's Exceptional Public Achievement Award",
         Answer : "June Lockhart"
     },
     {
         Question : "Name the young actor featured in the episode 'The Challenge'?",
         Answer : "Kurt Russell"
     },
     {
         Question : "The Robot was created by the same person that created Robby the Robot.  What is the creator's name?",
         Answer : "Robert Kinoshita"
     },
     {
         Question: "In the (infamous) episode 'Great Vegetable Rebellion' Dr. Smith is turned into which vegetable?",
         Answer : "Celery"
     },
     {
         Question:"In the episode 'Space Beauty' which Robinson sibling is forced into the beauty pageant?",
         Answer : "Judy"
     },
     {
         Question:"What actress also appeared in 'The Sound of Music'?",
         Answer : "Angela Cartwright"
     },
     {
         Question :"What was the name of the pilot, played by Mark Goddard?",
         Answer : "Don West"
     },
     {
         Question : "What actor also appeared in three episodes of 'The Twilight Zone'?",
         Answer : "Billy Mummy"
     },
     {
        Question : "What Space Adventure show was pitched to CBS but declined due to 'Lost in Space'?",
        Answer : "Star Trek"
    },
    {
        Question : "The computers used in 'Lost in Space' are of what brand (yes, they were authentic)?",
        Answer : "Burroughs"
    },
    {
        Question : "Who was the voice of the Robot?",
        Answer : "Dick Tufield"
    },
    {
        Question : "The spaceship is referred to as the Jupiter, but what was the original name?",
        Answer : "Gemini"
    },
    {
        Question : "This character from 'Lost in Space' was ranked on the list of '25 Greatest Sci-Fi Legends' (TV Guide, they are still around?)?",
        Answer : "The Robot"
    },
    {
        Question : "Angela Cartwright (Penny) starred in what early television show?",
        Answer : "Make Room for Daddy"
    }






]

module.exports = lostInSpaceArray;